lincmedia.co.jp 2008-06-24

# LINC Media - Privacy Policy

In addition to complying with the Law Concerning Protection of Personal Information (the "Personal Information Protection Law") and all other laws and regulations regarding the handling of personal information, LINC Media Inc. will comply with this privacy policy. 

Acquisition of Personal Information LINC Media Inc. will only acquire personal information by legitimate means. 

Purpose of Use of Personal Information LINC Media Inc. will use the personal information we acquire for one or more of the following purposes. Except where permitted under the Personal Information Protection Law or any other relevant law or regulation, we will not use an individual's personal information for any purpose outside of those listed below, without that individual's prior consent. 

  * Conducting LINC Media's business matching services; Personal information may be shown to LINC Media's client companies for business matching purpose only an individual company wish to receive business matching service 
  * Sending (by mail, fax, e-mail or other means) articles and other Useful information; Notification of seminars and other events; 
  * Responding to inquiries; and 

Any other purpose incidental to those listed above. 

Provision of Personal Information to Third Parties LINC Media Inc. will comply with the Personal Information Protection Law and all other relevant laws and regulations regarding the provision of personal information to third parties. 

Safekeeping of Personal Information LINC Media Inc. will handle all personal information in an appropriate manner, and put in place proper measures to prevent the disclosure or loss of, tampering with, or damage to, any personal information in our custody, through the implementation of operational procedures and the instruction of our staff. 

Access Log Information 

Our Web server collects access logs containing the following information, viewer's domain, IP address, type of browser and time of access. This data may be used by us and our agents for the following purposes: 

Web site and system administration. Research and development of web site usage. Anonymous user analysis. This access log has been marked as non-identifiable. This means that there is no reasonable way for the site to identify the individual person this data was collected from.
